I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
（蘭(らん)）あそこのステージで お前は
ダイブリとセッションするんだ
That's the stage where you'll
do a session with Dying Breed.
（栄二(えいじ)）信じられません
彼らとやれるなんて…
I can't believe...
that I can play with them.
We need a huge event
for Belle Ame's debut.
（蘭）ベルアームのデビューには
大きなイベントが必要なんだぞ
（栄二）本当に感謝してます
I'm really grateful to you.
（蘭）栄二 これはビジネスなんだ
Eiji, this is business.
さすがに全米で800万枚売る
バンドのマネージャーだ
That manager was just what I expected
of a manager of an 8 million-seller band.
Our talks went smoothly.
（蘭）話はスムーズだったよ
"Live 12
'Secret Live"'
（エディ：英語）〈その
バンドは いけているのかい？〉
Hey, is that band any good?
（ケビン：英語）
〈もちろんだよ エディ〉
Of course, Eddy.
These guys are the
next big thing in Japan.
〈彼らは日本のレコード会社の
イチオシの新人なんだ〉
（エディ）〈ケビンは
相変わらず強引だな〉
Kevin, you're pushy.
〈どうするマット？〉
What do you think, Matt?
If we like them at the rehearsal...
yeah, we could play with them.
（マット：英語）
〈リハで気に入ったら—〉
〈一緒にやってもかまわない〉
〈カモーン
これはビジネスなんだ 頼むよ〉
Come on. This is business. For me!
Hm...What are they called?
（マット）
〈そのバンド何ていうんだ？〉
〈ベルアーム〉
Belle Ame...It means
"beautiful spirit" in French.
〈フランス語で
“美しい魂”っていう意味だとさ〉
〈おいジム 撮るのはやめてくれ〉
Hey, Jim! Don't film me.
〈やめてくれよ〉
Bugger off. Hit the road!
Why? Why not? I should let
everyone know how smart you are.
（ジム：英語）〈いいじゃないか〉
〈君がいかに優秀か
皆に教えてやろうぜ！〉
-No. Eddy...Can you tell him not to?
-Come on, over here.
（ケビン）〈ノー エディ〉
〈ヤツに
何とか言ってくれないか？〉
-Jim, give me that...
-Come on.
Give me that camera. I'll kick your ass.
I told you not to film.
〈うつすなって言っただろ〉
（竜介(りゅうすけ)）えーっと—
Uh...Eddy's guests...six of us.
エディのゲストで
BECK(ベック) ６人です
"Registration for Participants"
Uh...Eddy's guests...six of us.
All right. Please sign here.
（スタッフ）はい それじゃ ここに
名前をお願いします
（千葉(ちば)）おっしゃー！
Awright!
（サク）竜介君…
Ryusuke-kun...
（千葉）おい コユキ！
Hey, Koyuki!
（千葉）さあ 飛びつけ！
Come on. Come at me.
（コユキ）千葉くーん
Chiba-kun!
-Oh!
-Taa!
（コユキ）あー いってー…
Ouch!
（コユキ）見えないよ…
-I can't see...
-Koyuki!
（真帆(まほ)）コユキー！
もっと前に行くぞ！
I'm going further up front!
（男性客１）おお 歯で弾いてる
-Oh...He's playing with his teeth.
-They're starting with
an imitation of Jimi Hendrix?
（男性客２）
いきなりジミヘンの真似かよ
Another minute, feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
No guarantees, but I'm so sure
She's into silence, candy for the head
Had a waking vision
I been so high ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly,
you gotta let go
Simply the most big sensation
once you're here you won't go back
She's really pretty, one-eyed vision
lose the fear it don't come back
Little sister showed me,
really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
Yeah, when I found you
My world came crashin' down
once you're here you won't go back
lose the fear it don't come back
コユキ あの人知ってる？
Koyuki, do you know who that is?
（コユキ）え…
ミュージシャンなの？
Hmm...Is he a musician?
（真帆）映画監督の
ジム・ウォルシュ 28歳
He's the movie director Jim Walsh-
28 years old.
He's a brilliant filmmaker from New York.
ニューヨークから現れた映像の天才
（コユキ）何でその人が？
Why's he here?
（真帆）ダイブリのツアームービー
撮ってるんだ
He's shooting Dying Breed's tour.
〈ここで飛び入りの
ゲストを紹介します〉
I'd like to introduce our
special guest who just came in.
〈ミスター エイジ・キムラ〉
Mr. Eiji Kimura.
フン
（ケビン）フン
（蘭）フッ フフフ…
（栄二）ついに来たぜ
I'm finally here...
（マット）ヘーイ！
Hey! You really sucked at the rehearsal.
（栄二）俺のストラトが…
My Strat!
Your music won't save anybody.
〈お前の音楽じゃ 結局
誰１人救えないぜ〉
〈消えな！〉
Fuck off!
Hey, hey...They don't understand
the situation right here.
〈おいおい 観客は状況を
理解してねえぞ〉
（竜介：英語）
〈どうすんだ エディ〉
What'cha gonna do now, Eddy?
ええ？
（マット）カモーン
-Huh?!
-Come on!
（真帆）マットはコユキを
呼んでるんだよ
Matt's calling you, Koyuki.
〈さぁ 俺たちと歌ってくれよ〉
All right. You gotta sing with us.
（男性客１）おい見ろよ
Hey, look!
（男性客２）誰だあ？
-Who's that?
-He's Japanese.
（女性客）日本人よ
（男性客３）まだ子どもだぜ
He's still a kid!
Hey, what'cha gonna play, dude?
（エディ）〈コユキ〉
Koyuki, what's your
favorite song of Dying Breed?
〈俺たちの曲で
好きな歌は何だい？〉
（コユキ）ええ…？
（真帆）好きな曲は何かって！
He's asking what your favorite song is!
ムーン・オン・ザ・ウォーター
Moon on the Water...
because I have special memory...
ビコーズ
アイ ハブ スペシャル メモリー
Full moon sways
Gentl...
〈なんだ？ こりゃ
マットのおふざけかい？〉
What was that?
A Matt's joke or something?
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day
On my way
Looking for a moment with my dear
Full moon waves
Slowly on the surface of the lake
You were there
Smiling in my arms for all those years
What a fool
I don't know 'bout tomorrow
What it's like to be
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Old love affair
Floating like a bird resting her wings
Well, I don't blame him.
（ミッちゃん）
まあ 仕方ねえけどな
He got up on the stage
with Dying Breed, after all.
なんてったって ダイブリと
ステージに立ったんだもんな
But it's been a week.
（千葉）でも もう１週間だぜ
A guitar expresses personality
through its six strings.
ギターってのは たった６本の弦を
伝わって出てくる人間性なんだ
ねえ 竜介君 英語で言ってよ
Come on, Ryusuke...Say it in English.
Listen, Koyuki! You already had me
say it a hundred times. Quit it, will you?
（竜介）おい コユキ
俺 もう100回は言わされてるぜ
勘弁してくれよ
"A guitar..."
ギターっていうのは…
He's weird...
気持ちワリィ
Hi!
（真帆）ハーイ！
-Ray, we're in trouble.
-Maho is.
（ヨシト：英語）
〈レイ やばいよ 真帆のヤツさ〉
-What? What's wrong?
-Uh-uh.
〈どうしたんだよ？〉
Hey, Yoshito...You tell
everything to my bro, huh?
（真帆：英語）〈おい ヨシト！〉
〈お前なぁ 何でも兄貴に
言いつける気か？〉
Yoshito's dad appears
in nine dramas every week.
ヨシトのオヤジさん
ゴールデンのドラマに出てるんだぜ
Yeah. I heard that from Maho.
ああ… 真帆から聞いたよ
おい ヨシト
Hey, Yoshito! This guy sang at
Dying Breed's secret live performance.
こいつ ダイブリの
シークレットライブで歌ったんだぜ
（ヨシト）ふ～ん
You know...My dad brought
an actress to my house last day...
〈この前さぁ オヤジのヤツ
女優連れてきてさ〉
-Who was it?
-Guess who...
（友人：英語）〈誰だよ それ？〉
（コユキ）あれは
どういう意味だったんだろう…
I wonder what that was all about...
（斎藤(さいとう)）何だって!?
What's that?!
You mean we can't enter
the singing contest this year?!
（斎藤）それじゃ 今年の
歌謡コンテストには—
参加できないって言うのか？
What do you mean,
the Neighborhood Board Chair is mad?
町内会長が怒ってる？
誰だそいつはー！
We've been practicing like crazy every day.
Shut up, will you? You nitwit!
連日猛練習してんだぞ
いい加減にしろ このバカチンが！
What's this all about?
どういうことなんだよ！
なあ こらー！
あ… アハハ…
Long time no see.
（泉(いずみ)）久しぶりだね
久しぶり…
Nice to see you.
I was in the neighborhood,
so I decided to stop by.
（泉）ちょっと近くに来たからさ
寄ってみたんだ
You've been well?
（コユキ）元気？
Yeah...You look well too, Koyuki.
コユキも元気そうじゃない
I heard from Kayo-chan.
You sang with Dying Breed?
（泉）カヨちゃんに聞いたよ
ダイブリのライブで
歌ったんだってね
That's awesome!
すごいじゃん
Yeah...Matt called me up.
（コユキ）うん
マットが誘ってくれたんだ
（泉）ねえ コユキ…
背伸びたんじゃない？
Say, Koyuki...Haven't you grown a little?
（コユキ）あ 斎藤さんにも
同じこと言われた
Saito-san said the same thing to me.
何か 大人っぽくなったね
You seem more grown up.
Hmm...Maybe it's because I'm being
forced to swim 3 kilometers every day.
ん～ 強いて言えば
毎日３キロは泳がされてますから
I see...I haven't swum
for a while. I wish I could.
そっか～
私も久しぶりに泳ぎたいな
But I haven't got a swimsuit.
でも水着ないんだよね～
You don't swim?
（コユキ）泳がないの？
Then tomorrow...
じゃ あした—
Shall we go to buy me a swimsuit?
水着買いに行こうか
"Summer Sale"
I wonder if it's a little too small.
（泉）ちょっと小さいかな？
Well, it had been quite a while...
（コユキ）だって ホント…
久しぶりだったから…
あ ごめん 何か変なこと言って…
I'm sorry if I said
anything I shouldn't...
彼氏と別れたんだ…
（コユキ）えっ…
-I broke up with my boyfriend...
-Huh?
No more gloomy subjects.
（泉）暗い話題はおしまい！
ん んん… ハァ～
Say...Let's go swimming!
ねえ 泳ぎ行こ！
The public pool's closed today.
きょうは市営プール 休みだよ
Oh, Yukio...A girl named Maho's
been calling for you.
（コユキの母）ああ 幸雄
真帆って子から何回も電話あったよ
What? If she calls again,
tell her I'll call her back later.
（コユキ）え？
またかかってきたら—
あとで こっちからかけるって
言っといて！
（コユキ）
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…
If you don't come, I'll go alone.
（泉）コユキが来なくても
私は１人で行ってるね
It's been a year since then...
あれから１年か…
Izumi-chan!
泉ちゃん！
コユキ 来てくれたんだ
Oh, you're here, Koyuki!
"School Facility-No Trespassing"
-Hurray!
-If you talk too loudly, they'll catch us.
やったー！
（コユキ）ああ… 声大きいと
バレちゃうよ
"School Facility-No Trespassing"
（泉）分かる？ あんまり
膝を曲げると勢いなくなっちゃうの
Do you understand? If you bend your knees
too much it'll slow you down.
Uh-huh...
Koyuki...
コユキは…
Do you like Maho-chan?
真帆ちゃんのこと好き？
Huh?
I'm talking about the
singing contest last year.
（泉）去年の
歌謡コンテストのこと
I heard about it from Saito-san
a long time ago.
（泉）ずっと前に
斎藤さんから聞いたんだ
I have a feeling she likes you.
（泉）彼女はコユキのこと
好きなんじゃないかな
（泉）私は 自分の気持ちに
気づくのが遅かったみたい
I guess I realized how I felt too late.
I was fool
（真帆）♪「MOON ON THE WATER」
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Old love affair
Floating like a bird resting her wings
U-Uh...
"Fireworks"
"Fishing Hole"
All right. Thank you very much!
（千葉）ははーい それじゃ
よろしくお願いしまーす…
"Fishing Hole"
So, what did they want?
（平(たいら)）で 何だって？
They want to hear Beck's demo tape.
BECKのデモテープが
聴きたいんだってさ
Yahoo!
イヤッホ～イ！ ハハハ…
-Hey, watch out!
-Alright!
（平）おい 危ねえだろ
（千葉）やったー
ハハハ… フフフ…
Anyway, thanks to Koyuki,
Beck's riding a big wave.
とにかくコユキのおかげで—
（千葉）やったー
ハハハ… フフフ…
BECKにもデカい波が
やってきたんだよな
（千葉）やったー
ハハハ… フフフ…
Music fans around the world
received shocking news today.
（アナウンサー）世界中の
音楽ファンに—
"Charismatic Singer Commits Suicide"
Music fans around the world
received shocking news today.
衝撃が走りました
"Charismatic Singer Commits Suicide"
-Last night in New York,
-What?
アメリカの
人気女性歌手—
-Last night in New York,
-What?
ワット!?
エリカ・
ブライジさんが—
現地時間の昨夜未明—
Popular American singer Ms. Erica Blige
killed herself in her hotel room
宿泊していた
ニューヨークのホテルの一室で—
ピストル自殺を遂げました
with a pistol.
Ms. Erica, a charismatic singer
with many fans in Japan,
エリカさんは 日本でも多くの
ファンを持つカリスマ的歌姫で—
had CD sales of over 20 million worldwide.
全世界で2,000万枚を超える
ＣＤのセールスを誇っています
According to a spokesman, her new album
was to be released in a few months...
関係者筋の話では—
数か月後にニューアルバムの発売と
全米ツアーが…
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Sunfish are cute, aren't they?
（千葉）
マンボウってさ—
かわいいよね
"Live 13 'Ciel Bleu"'
Sunfish are cute, aren't they?
I wonder if they're edible...
あれって 食えんのか？